I say good night, good night, I
request that there are
some things here which we do
not do properly, like I do not go to the officer quickly,
otherwise people will say that she was a girl, let's go director,
how did you like this, but I
can take her back sometime by doing Praya plus along with the trees,
listening to this we listen a little more
[Music]
[Applause] so that we do
not feel the lack of this, sometimes if
mother becomes less and emotional then that is
graduation day celebration at Shiv, that is why she
works hard to get the full amount, then she should
say it, right, from this plane,
audience, promise yourself that you will only say it,
wish you happy birthday